Kevin Rehberg

Full-Stack Web Developer

Contact

Address

West Palm Beach, FL, 33415

Phone

(954) 534-6295

E-mail

krehberg12@gmail.com

Skills

Typescipt

3KIIIS	
React	
	Excellent
Next.js	
	Excellent
Git	
	Excellent
Redux	
	Very Good
Node	
- Frances	Very Good
Express	
	Very Good
PHP	
	Very Good
MongoDB	
	Good

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Able to handle any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 3 years of related experience.

Work History

2017-03 -Current

Remote WordPress Developer

Rabid Minds, Philadelphia, PA

- Created and updated re-usable code libraries to streamline WordPress development cycle.
- Leveraged strong understanding of WordPress core to manipulate admin and theme components.
- Converted design assets into component-based HTML,
 CSS and JavaScript.
- Collaborated with designers and project manager on project specifications, strategy and execution to build new WordPress pages and update existing ones.
- Installed required plugins and additional coding to fit final design and functionality requirements.

2018-06 -2021-01

Front-End Developer

NG Web Services, Delray Beach, FL

- Worked in Agile-driven environment to effectively maintain project timelines and utilize available resources.
- Conceived and built optimized landing pages in HTML and CSS, including API integration and cross-browser compatibility, to support marketing.
- Reviewed code to validate structures, assess security and verify browser, device and operating system compatibility.
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.

Education

2016-06 -2017-12

Good

Network Engineering

Valencia College - Orlando, FL